All our workers should get
any kind of insurance done through
both online and offline methods.
All the people are getting calls through the insurance company
because this is an important information for the customers also
because many times
we hear that a
call came from
someone else and
we
know that
if you take the policy online, there are
third party persons whom you can never even see.
If you
do Panchayat through telemarketer then you can definitely buy them.
At the time of service,
you will not get that information there
because the information about the policy will be through someone else. The
result of the policy will be
available through someone else when we have